[{"answer": "No you didn't", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "How do you know", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yea, like my friend before you. You are experiencing a second revival", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Nay, their eyes are not yet prepared to see the likes of me", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What's the matter, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "...Okay, that makes sense. Mine is going swimmingly, too", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "How's it going", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why bad", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Your little girlfriend, my friend", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Look, my friend. Do you really know what a period is", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Poo pants", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Pooped pants", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Pooped 'nmuh pants", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Poo pants", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yuh you pooped your pants", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Pooped 'nmuh pants", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Pooped in my pants", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes, puberty is a very wonderful thing, my friend. It'w what links us all together, makes us one", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Never went through puberty? Who never went through puberty", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So what are we gonna do for New Year's", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Aaaargh. I'm gonna go take some more hormones", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend, why does God hate me", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He hates me more. He doesn't answer my prayers. I prayed to him every day and he never answered me", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, yeah, but just because God doesn't answer your prayers doesn't mean he doesn't care about you", "docId": "South-Park-Are-You-There-God_-It_s-Me_-Jesus!.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, God can't just answer every prayer and suddenly give you everything you want. That takes all the living out of life", "qsentId": 26}]